#### ROBERT ZACCHIGNA

#### About - Robert-Zacchigna.github.io | Contact - Robert-Zacchigna.github.io

#### **SUMMARY**



Over 4 years of IT experience, 2 years of professional experience working for Discover Financial Services as a Data Engineer developing pipelines for cloud technologies and 2 years working for Illinois State University as a System Administrator managing various enterprise applications. I am also a member of the National Society of Collegiate Scholars (NSCS).

#### **EDUCATION**

June 2019 – Bellevue University

November 2021 Masters Of Science – Data Science

August 2015 –

Illinois State University

June 2019

Bachelors Of Science - Systems Development/Analytics

Minor in Business – Business Administration

### **TECHNOLOGY**

#### Languages

 $\cdot$  Python – 3+ years  $\cdot$  Spark – 0.5+ years  $\cdot$  SQL/NoSQL – 1.5+ years  $\cdot$  R – 1+ years

· Java – 1+ years

#### Software

Microsoft Excel,Word, Outlook, OfficeSnowflakePyCharmRStudioVisual Studio

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## June 2019 – Present

Data Engineer, Discover Financial Services (DFS)

• Currently working as a Data engineer at DSF and it's my first full time position out of college. Main project includes on-boarding business users to cloud technologies to help develop pipelines to allow them to access the data that they need using cloud based tools.

## August 2017 – May 2019

System Administrator, Illinois State University at Administrative Technologies (AT)

· Worked as a Sys Admin for AT maintaining (users, security, app updating, etc.) different apps used throughout the university.

# May 2017 – August 2017

System Administrator Intern, Illinois State University at Administrative Technologies (AT)

• System Administrator role; learned about the various apps the university uses and how to properly maintain and handle security for each app.